Good morning.
It's Kosaku Kawajiri.
I apologize for the
inconvenience but I'll be
arriving at the office
about 15 minutes late.
My son is misbehaving and I must educate
him on the finer points
of familiar respect.
Yes, I understand.
The matter is inconsequential from
the perspective of a business owner.
Right.
My deepest apologies.
Yes, of course.
Thank you, sir.
I'll handle my son straight away.
Once that's done, I'll head to the office.
Yes, sir.
Got it.
Thank you for your understanding.
Damn Kosaku Kawajiri.
What an obsequious little drip.
You were just a socially anxious nitwit.
Why would you want to
climb the corporate ladder?
Josuke thinks he's so clever.
It's clear that he only hid
inside that house because he
thinks he'll have the advantage
in a close combat battle.
Admittedly, there's a kernel
of truth in that belief.
If I want to survive this skirmish,
I'd be wise to avoid shining
diamond like the plague.
If I can pinpoint Josuke's location,
I can launch an air bullet from
here and possibly make contact.
Alright.
Hey, you! Hmm?
This is private property.
Why are you creeping around here?
What's that supposed to mean?
You trying to say you ain't trespassing?
Okay, then I have some
questions for you, smartass.
Is this your house?
How long have you been watching?
Just a minute!
I'm asking the questions around here!
And I happen to live next door!
I was taking a nap, but someone started
making a damn commotion and woke me up!
I've got my eye on you, creeper!
Lovely Ryo lives here, and she said
someone keeps stealing her underwear!
And it just so happens
no one's home now, perv!
It must be nice.
Huh?
Having all that free time.
Hey, you're walking away!
Damn bastard!
How dare you prey on sweet Ryo like that!
What a smarmy dick!
That perverted panty plunderer is sick.
These silky skivvies must
They must be real?
Oh, boy!
Such pure, pristine panties!
It's my lucky day!
You Beat goza sui yuki.
Saqqara shio kaze?
Tonneru nukete tome!
Cairo konichi.
Mayoyakomu.
Kokoro ni.
Toke Kick Cujoh.
Crazy on kono spirit?
With that, we're not going to be a star.
Let the voice of love take you higher.
The 99th is your song.
We're going to be the next time.
She returns!
Crap! It's no use!
The phone line's been cut!
Okoyasu's dead.
Which leaves me no choice.
I'm going to use Shining Diamond to
wipe Yoshikage Kira off the planet.
He's plagued us long enough.
I'm putting an end to this evil.
Hayato.
Hide against the wall till this is over.
I don't want Kira laying eyes on you.
Now which way?
Which direction is he gonna attack from?
What?!
Hey, look out!
It's an air bullet and it's
moving right towards you!
Get out of the way!
It's about the same size
as the one from before!
But I don't get it!
How in the world was he able to track
you down from all the way out there?!
This doesn't make any sense!
Freaking great I see you
Josuke Higashikata I know
the exact distance between
us three meters until impact
there's
the culprit
and if I can see it now
that means Josuke can too
Yes now you can Dodge it!
No matter how many of those he
shoots, you can get out of the way!
What the hell?
Wait, is it able to trace Josuke?
That hand-hoardin' killer's found
a way to track my movements.
Where is he?
How can he see me?
Hey that room doesn't have any windows and
where there are windows
the curtains are drawn.
There's no way he could have seen
you from outside it must be automated
it's following You on autopilot no i
don't think so deadly queen already
has a homing device it's an Annoying
little heat seeker called heart
attack just look this bullet is
completely ignoring the Lit cigarettes i
don't know all the details but i'm
willing to bet if it was a homing
device The air bullet couldn't
penetrate the wall and think about it if
this thing Really was automated Kira
wouldn't always need to hit the kill
switch Himself ship bricks how the
hell does he know exactly where i am
You have to find Kira figure out
how the hell he's watching me
He's right outside the gate two more
meters to go and then kaboom
are you? Are you serious?
I'm sorry, Chosuke, I don't get how he's
tracking you from all the way out there!
Start running!
Bastard, being a creepy
voyeur is freaky enough.
One meter to go.
But you've crossed into being a
stalker tracking my every move,
and that's just a bridge too far.
Shining Diamond!
Contact is imminent.
Detonate!
I finally managed to get a clean hit.
Deadly queen.
Wow, I narrowly escaped death!
But luckily I was prepared.
You're a true warrior.
And you'll fight the good
fight to the bitter end!
I know better than to get close to you.
Josuke Higashikata.
Josuke!
Whoa!
He's still alive!
A direct hit, yet he remains fully intact.
There's a slight lag when I
manually detonate the bomb,
but its potential to cause
damage is unparalleled.
My next attack is going to seal the deal!
Please!
I need you to get up now!
We have to find somewhere safe to hide!
We're going the wrong direction.
I have to go back. Huh?
We're going the wrong way! Turn back!
I have to bash his brains in.
Bring me to that bastard Yoshikage Kira!
My shining diamond can heal.
But its power won't work on me.
That said, all the blood I lost
earlier has dried and hardened.
It's matter like any other.
It's just not a part of me anymore.
I can grab a whole bunch of it
and stick it to whatever I want.
In fact, I trapped some
inside a chunk of glass.
The rain stopped, so that blood stain on
his jacket should be good and dry by now.
Behold my wondrous creation!
It's my own homemade homing missile.
What the hell?
That was the piece of glass
I flicked away earlier!
The blood on my jacket!
The damn glass was pulled to the blood,
turning it into a jacket bullet! Whoa!
You got him good!
The projectile launched
itself right in his back!
That's…
His shining diamond is really
starting to irritate me!
That damn stand is
completely unpredictable.
Even so, after my attack, Jousuke's
in much worse shape than me.
One more shot, just one more shot, and
Yoshikage Kira will bask in victory!
Jousuke, it's here!
Man, I've never seen
him make one this big!
I guess he's not messing around.
This has got to be his last-ditch attack.
Well, two can play at that game.
Here we go!
What are you doing?
The same attack isn't going
to work on Kira twice.
You know that.
He'll deflect it.
Maybe he will. Huh?
But we'll never know until we try, right?
By the way, Hayato,
I'm sorry to bother you, but I put that
lighter I was using back in my pocket.
Grab it for me.
I'd do it myself.
But this piece of wood stuck in my
side is kind of getting in my way.
You don't need to make smoke anymore.
or you can already see
the air bullet, right?
You've got it all wrong.
I'm not using the lighter
to see the bullets.
It's for something else entirely.
Trust me here.
Time's come.
I have to find out how
he knows where I am.
Stay very still, Hayato.
Oh, Josuke, what the heck are you?
Hold it right there, Hayato.
I'm starting to get the feeling and
he's not observing us with his eyes.
He may be listening to our every move.
Kira was clutching a cell phone.
Simple coincidence?
Yeah, right.
So who was on the other end of that call?
His boss from the office?
Nah.
There's only one person in the world
Kira would call at a time like this.
I'd almost forgotten about you
floating around, you crusty old man.
Yoshikage Kira's one and only
savior, his pathetic father.
Wow, I had no idea he'd
snuck his way into my pocket.
So that's it.
Now we have our answer.
Oh no!
It's the air bullet!
It passed right through the window!
Get back!
It connected!
I see Josuke.
He's currently fleeing
three meters forward.
I don't believe it!
It completely bypassed him!
Keep going.
Now the fool's moving to the right and up.
Three meters.
He hasn't figured out it's Josuke
pretending to be his father!
Change of plans. To the left.
Move one meter.
Almost there.
What in the hell?
You are such a duplicitous dickhead!
Bullseye.
Press the button.
GUSHIKANI!
Tell me, did that vaporize
Josuke? Is he dead?
Yeah, you splattered the room with him.
Now, he's floating in the great beyond.
But he was already a ghost,
so it's more like you shipped him off
to the big nursing home in the sky.
Josuke.
Josuke!
Impossible.
This has to be some kind of mistake.
How could this be happening to me?
I was supposed to live a peaceful, quiet
life, like a flower in a tranquil field.
Suffering like this was
never part of the plan.
I'm Yoshikage Kira, damn it!
I can't lose heart now.
Whatever happens, I must keep a cool head.
It's trying times like these
that truly test your mettle.
I know it seems like
things can't get any worse,
but it'll all work out
just like every other time.
Even though life has me
backed into a corner,
my wits will turn this bout
of adversity into opportunity.
That is what Yoshikage Kira does.
It's what he excels at.
This is my world, my reality,
and there's nothing in my world
that I can't find a way to surmount!
You stepped into my range.
Big mistake, Yoshikage Kira.
I can't believe it!
He took the bait and Josuke was able
to close the distance between them!
Now that it's close-quarter combat,
this will be over in no time!
Josuke definitely has the upper hand,
but if Kira so much as grazes him,
he'll turn him into a human bomb!
And if that wasn't bad enough,
that explosion from earlier really
damaged Josuke's leg inside!
He shouldn't even be
able to stand right now!
What are we gonna do?!
That's enough!
I'm ending you!
Then bring it on. I'm ready.
Now, call out, deadly queen!
Deadly queen!
Buddha!
Shit!
He's dropped!
I'm going to die!
This brat is actually going to kill me!
Wait, what?
No way!
When did he do that?
He was so close to winning!
Chosuke was totally overpowering Kira!
Oh no, was he right?
Could luck really be on
that murderer's side?
What all that punching
and I didn't connect
they were blocked by the air bullets.
But how I never intended to use them as
protection I didn't have time to act.
Stray cat I understand stray
cat anticipated the incoming
flurry of blows and then
protected itself instinctively.
It's time I have to make this work once
again adversity invites opportunity.
Let's finish them off deadly
queen make that air bullet a bomb.
Victory it's now an explosive and at this
distance your death is all but assured.
With the injuries you've got you don't
have the ability to avoid my attack.
This is the end for you.
Damn you, Kira!
A contact explosive?! Josuke!
Quick, you have to grab a
piece of glass or wood to use!
Whack it and take cover!
I win!
I've come out on top just like every other
time my back has been against the wall!
My guardian angel never fails,
your fate has been sailed, boy!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!
What's going on?!
Check out the air bullet!
For some reason it's changed course!
You're dead!
How is he?
Is this really happening?
Okuyasu! You're alive!
Wow, this power!
It always blows my mind.
I've thought about it really hard,
but I still can't figure out where the
hand puts all the stuff it scrapes away?
Although I've never been
the best at using my brain,
so I guess that's no big surprise.
Off you go!
How the hell did you?!
It's Okuyasu!
He's as good as new!
But I'm positive his heart stopped
beating and he for sure wasn't breathing!
Oh man, that dream was freaky as hell.
I was walking around in this dark open
space when I suddenly saw this bright light.
The source of that light was
my brother, Big Bro Keicho.
He asked me where I was
planning to go next.
I told him, I'm going with you, Big Bro.
Even as snot-nosed brats,
I could count on my bro.
He made the best decisions, so I
always knew I was in good hands.
Then he said something I never expected.
You have to decide.
Okuyasu, wherever you go, you are
the master of your own journey.
I thought about that real hard.
And as soon as I said I was going back
to Mariah, I woke up in the house.
I had all sorts of sad feelings, though.
Okuyasu.
Hey, newsflash, Einstein.
This ain't the time to drone on
about your bro and see in the light.
Uh-oh, seems like
someone's in a shitty mood.
Those injuries must not be too bad, since
you still have enough energy to be a dick.
Shut your face!
If you were alive all along, why
didn't you open your eyes, dumbass?
No, impossible!
Ever since I was a little child,
luck has always been on my side!
I've never run out of luck
and I refuse to start now!
Fire another bomb, stray
cannon, make it count!
What?
Whoa, there little dude, easy!
You did it!
We've got Kira now!
Thanks to you, he won't be able to
use his air bullets as explosives!
It makes no sense.
How has it come to this?
Fools!
Yoshikage Kira's never met a
problem he couldn't conquer!
You won't do me in! Mr.
Jojaro, look!
It looks like the bang came
from that house way over there.
It sounded like some kind
of big gas explosion.
Hey, that man needs help!
Just look, he's been injured!
What in the world?
It's Josuke and Okuyasu!
That kid they're with,
it's Hayato Kawajiri.
And the man bleeding
out is Kosaku Kawajiri.
The puzzle pieces are falling into place.
It doesn't matter if you
have some guardian angel.
Your lucky break is about
to come to a painful end!
Nothing you've got compares to
these guys' righteous hearts!
They're gonna make you pay!
Can you feel it, Yoshikage Kira?
The truth is staring
you right in the face!
You're nothing compared to them!
And if it happens again,
I'm going to move so slightly
to the arms and the lips
and the face of the humic
and the ball that I need to,
I want to come and stand
a little bit closer,
breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you.
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you, but ooh,
I've got to find out.
Ooh, I want you, I don't know if I need
you, but ooh, I've got to find out.